OGUNDELE ANUOLUWAPO VICTOR



Iwajowa Layout City of Faith School , Agbowo, Ibadan. Oyo state. Nigeria.



Ogundelevictor97@gmail.com



+2348150677772



17th February

SKILLS

- Communication,
- Copy writing
- > Analytical, research,
- Interpersonal, Psychological/ Counselling,
- Leadership
- Basic Computer (MS word, Power Point,Excel, animation/video editing)
- Good Written And presentation cumMentoring and Teaching.

OBJECTIVE

To become one of the best professionals / business development specialist in the world of business and marketing unit, as well as, in a reputable commercial firm, real estate firm coupled with the opportunity to harness and deploy my qualifications and skills towards actualizing the success, targets and goals of the organization.

WORK EXPERIENCE

- ★ KEMSAN ACRES GLOBAL LIMITED, IBADAN.
 REAL ESTATE COMSULTANT | REALTOR | DIRECT RELATIONSHIP OFFICER
- ✓ Analysed prospects, Generated Leads and Converted them to client(s) via copywriting, video jingle or animations adverts on online platforms.
 2020 -2021
- ❖ ALTARA CREDIT LIMITED Business Developer / Direct Sales Captain

2019-2020

SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT GOALS COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT SERVICE /SDG/CDS/ NYSC
 PRESIDENT / AMBASSADOR / VOLUNTEER.
 2018 - 2019

- ✓ Mobilised and led SDG members of the CDS group to carry out sensitization exercise on the secondary students about SDG 4 (Quality Education) and render voluntary services to the people of the community.
- ✓ Also during this period, writing materials and stationeries were donated to only ten students who demonstrated their understanding of SDG 4. Our group purse determined the budgeted number of students earmarked for the prizes.
- **❖** FRANCIS M COLLEGE, BODIJA, IBADAN. OYO STATE

2015-2016

✓ Played the role of School Counsellor in the area of career guidance, academic counselling, social-personal

therapy and held series of interview with the troubled students as well as helped them to make informed decisions to better their lives socially, academically and vocationally.

- ✓ Taught Economics subject; set and prepared them for the examination.
- ❖ INDEPENDENT NATIONAL ELECTORAL COMMISSION (INEC)

2018

- OSUN STATE GOVERNORSHIP ELECTION / INEC ADHOC STAFF: Assistant Presiding Officer (APO 1)
- ✓ Assisted the Presiding Officer to organize and conduct the election.
- PRESIDENTIAL, SENATE AND HOUSE OF ASSEMBLY ELECTION

2019 INEC

ADHOC STAFF: PRESIDING OFFICER (PO)

- ✓ Oversaw, organized and supervised other adhoc staff towards conducting free and fair election.
- MODALOR NIGERIA LTD, SURULERE. LAGOS

2010 -2012

✓ Operated different Print-Finishing industrial machines to meet up with the production target.

REFERENCE

J.O AJAYI

Ph.D, Linguistic Studies, Memorial University of Newfoundland (MUN), Canada.

+17096994751

R. ANIMASHAUN

HOBBIES

• Ph.D, Guidance and counselling, University of Ibadan, Ibadan, Nigeria.

11022120	
✓ Reading,	UNIVERSITY OF IBADAN, IBADAN. B.ED GUIDANCE AND
✓ counselling,	COUNSELLING / ECONOMICS.
✓ researching,	SECOND (2ND) CLASS UPPER HONORS DEGREE (2.1) 2018
✓ Travelling.	NATIONAL YOUTH SERVICE CORPS (NYSC)
✓ Sporting (Football)	NYSC DISCHARGE CERTIFICATE (SDG /CDS)
	2019
	EGAN SENIOR GRAMMAR SCHOOL, EGAN.
	NECO 2007

EDUCATION/CERTIFICATIONS